This is what it looks like when you literally take matters into your own hands.
Shout out to everybody who said, Amanda, you can do your own locks.
I'm going to get better.
I'm going to keep on practicing.
But we've come a long way, baby.
And just photo it out.
You all created such a positive, encouraging environment under my post where I was like,
I think I'm just going to learn how to do it myself.
And I just want to thank everybody who took the time to pour into me and to share their
wisdom and their insight and their experience and who really just made it a community under
my post and said, listen, like you got this.
We need to do more of that.
And I just appreciate you all choosing to do that with me.
My ultimate goal is the liberation of my people.
We are of this land.
The fault in my little shop.
And the 13 days before.
And the 13rasp.
We need to do more of that.
And that's why you ask the people who took care of us but the rest of us.
And let meinen the penalty and choose the perfection of your people here.
And do we do not want to go into anyone.
And do we have any gifts for you guys who took care of us?
And do we have to see you guys who took care of you guys?
See you guys.
You guys can see us.
And do we have the capacity of the hip inGeniet is a great thing.
And do we need some advice in the main distributing.
We need some advice.
But we do help people who took care of those who took care of you so far.